http://www.diamondheadtheatre.com/privacy-policy

Diamond Head TheatreMenuShowsPlay ArchiveAuditionsDonateAnnual GivingCapital CampaignProducer's ClubSponsorship'Ilima AwardsTicketsSeason Tickets FAQsBuy TicketsClassesOnline ClassesMTE - SummerMTE I MTE II InternshipScholarshipsInstructorsPoliciesShooting StarsRentalsCostume RentalsFacility RentalsAbout UsStaffBoard of DirectorsEncore NewsletterHistoryGet InvolvedYour New TheatrePrivacy Policy
PRIVACY NOTICE
We at Diamond Head Theatre (DHT) respect your concerns about privacy and value the trust you have placed in us.  This Privacy Notice describes the types of personal information we collect, how we may use that information, and with whom we may share it.  Our Privacy Notice also describes the measures we take to protect the security of the information.  In addition, we describe the choices you can make about how we use the information you provide to us.  We tell you how you can update your contact information, remove your name from our mailing list, or answer any questions you may have about our privacy practices.
What types of information does DHT collect about me and how does DHT use the information?
We collect and use information about you to communicate with you about our shows, classes and events. We also collect information to improve your website experience, enroll adults and children in classes, enable you to make donations to DHT, and enable contact with DHT. Here are the ways we obtain information about you and the types of information we obtain. We also tell you how we use the information.
Purchases When you purchase tickets, you choose to give us contact and payment information (such as credit card information) so we may process your order.  When you pay for a show ticket, a class or a special event, using a credit card, we use your credit card information only to fulfill your order and for other internal purposes.
Contact Us Link If you contact us via our website, we may ask you for information such as your name, address and email address so we can respond to your questions or comments.  Unless you consent, we do not retain this information except to respond to your inquiries.
Donations You also give us contact information and credit card or checking account information so we can process your donation. We use this information for that purpose and to customize our communication with you.
Frequently Asked Questions
Does DHT share the information it obtains about me with third parties?
DHT does not share personal information about you with any third parties.
How does DHT protect personal information?
The security of personal information is a high priority for us.  We maintain online safeguards to protect against unauthorized disclosure, use, alteration and destruction of the personal information in our possession.
How does DHT update its Privacy Notice?
DHT’s products, services, promotions and programs will change over time.  This Privacy Notice will be updated periodically to reflect those changes and corresponding changes in our information practices.  Whenever we revise this Privacy Notice, we will change the date on the notice to indicate when the revisions were made.  We reserve the right to change our information practices and the terms of this Privacy Notice, and to apply the changed practices to all information we have about you.
Does the DHT website contain links to other websites?
The DHT website may contain links to other websites that operate independently of DHT and are not under our control.  We provide links to those sites solely for your convenience and information.  Those sites have their own privacy notices, which we suggest you review if you visit any linked sites.  DHT is not responsible for information that is provided by those sites or for any other use of the sites.
How can I update my contact information?
Please email us to indicate that you would want to change the contact information we have for you.  Please email us from the email address we would have on file so we can verify ownership.
Email us at dht@diamondheadtheatre.com
Will I receive email from DHT?
We will send you email only if you have provided us with your email address and have asked us to communicate with you this way.
What if I prefer not to receive communications from DHT?
Please email us to indicate that you would like to unsubscribe from our mailings.  Please email us from the email address we would have on file so we can verify ownership.
Effective 9/1/09
